tjx.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy

Welcome to the TJX Corporate Website, the website for The TJX Companies, Inc. ("TJX"). TJX, T.J. Maxx, Marshalls, HomeGoods, Sierra Trading Post, and other affiliates are the "TJX Businesses." This Privacy Statement describes the type of personal information we collect on the website, how we may use that information, with whom we share that information, how we protect that information and how you can access and update your employment profile. 

####  Information We Collect 

We may collect certain personal information from you in connection with your activities that may include: 

#####  _Request Current Investor Information Online_

If you would like to request current investor information online, we ask you for information such as your name, telephone number, postal address, and e-mail address so we can provide you with the requested information. 

#####  _Apply for Funding from The TJX Foundation_

Certain qualified nonprofit organizations may apply for program funding from The TJX Foundation on tjx.com. As part of the review process, an eligibility questionnaire and an application is requested, which includes your organization's name, postal address, e-mail address, and taxpayer identification number, as well as the name and contact information for the organization's executive director, application preparer, and private grants specialist. 

#####  _Careers_

When you apply for a job at TJX or create a profile for employment purposes via the website, we may ask for the following information: 

  * Your name
  * Contact information, such as phone number, postal, or e-mail address
  * Employment/Education History (resume)

If you would like to send a job listing you found on the website to a friend, we may ask you to provide: 

  * Your friend's e-mail address
  * Your name
  * Your e-mail address

Additionally, we or companies acting on our behalf may collect certain computer and browser information through automated technologies such as cookies and web beacons when you visit our websites (whether or not you have signed in as a register user) or otherwise interact with us online. A "cookie" is a file that a website sends to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to identify the browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag, or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. 

The information collected using these tools may include your IP address, the address of the web page that referred you to our websites, dates and times of website visits and the location of your device. These automated technologies also permit the collection of "clickstream data," which may include a log of content you access while browsing a website. Companies acting on our behalf may combine the information collected from your visit to our website(s) with other information they have collected previously. 

####  Opt-Out From and/or Restrict Cookies 

Your web browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict, reject, or disable certain cookies (but please note that we do not respond to "Do Not Track" signals from web browsers). Additionally, you may opt-out of data collection from certain companies that we use to collect information. 

  * We use a company called Adobe to collect and analyze information about the use of our website(s). To learn more about Adobe’s collection and analysis of information by automated means, including how to opt out, click [here](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/analytics.html).
  * We also use a company called Google to collect and analyze information about the use of our website(s). This information helps us serve relevant advertisements to you on Google, and also helps us to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you have an account with Google, click [here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) to manage your advertising settings, otherwise you can manage these settings through your web browser as is described above.

####  How We Use the Information We Collect 

When we collect information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including to: 

  * Review and process your application for the position you posted for and if applicable, shared for other job opportunities
  * Respond to your comments and inquiries
  * Comply with your request for current investor information
  * Perform a review of eligibility for program funding from the TJX Foundation
  * Helps us understand website activity and improve your use of our website
  * Helps us prevent unauthorized activity, claims and other liabilities
  * Measure and manage the advertising effectiveness of our job postings and events
  * Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and our Terms of Use
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our talent acquisition process (including managing our communication and administering our website)

In addition, we use information collected online through automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users' visits to our websites or experience in a mobile app; (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users' interests and the manner in which our users browse or interact with us; (iii) measuring and managing the advertising effectiveness of our online and offline advertisements and events; and (iv) managing our business. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our websites and mobile apps, identify users of our websites and mobile apps, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our websites or our mobile apps, how users navigate through our websites and mobile apps, and how we may tailor our offerings to better meet the needs of our users. In order for us to maintain the accuracy of your personal information and improve our communication with you, we may also supplement the information we collect with other public demographic information. 

####  Information We Share 

We may share your information among TJX Businesses (which are affiliates owned by TJX, including T.J. Maxx, Marshalls, HomeGoods, Sierra Trading Post, Winners, HomeSense, and T.K. Maxx). They may use this information to offer products and services to you consistent with the purposes identified in this statement. Your information may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation) involving all or part of the TJX Businesses or as part of a stock sale or other change in corporate control. **  **

If a contest, sweepstakes or promotion is jointly-sponsored by us and one or more other sponsors, your information may be shared with such sponsors. We do not control other sponsors' use of your personal information, and their use of your information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to participate in such jointly sponsored contests, sweepstakes or promotions. Such offerings may also be subject to additional rules and regulations governing your participation.  

We may also share certain personal information we collect about you with partners or third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. For example, we may use third parties to host our websites or mobile apps, operate certain of its features, send e-mails, print or send mailings, run our sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, conduct customer research, authorize and process your payments, manage and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness, and fulfill orders. Such third-party service providers are given the information that they need to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own or any others' marketing purposes.

We may disclose information about you as is required by law or legal process such as subpoenas or court or agency orders, or as we may reasonably determine to be necessary or appropriate to protect our rights or the rights of others, to avert loss or harm to persons or property, to enforce our website Terms of Use or this Privacy Statement, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity.

####  Children's Privacy 

We do not seek nor will we knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. 

####  Links 

Our websites and mobile apps may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These linked websites operate independently from TJX and may have their own privacy statements or policies. Other linked websites may be owned or controlled by TJX but have privacy policies that differ from this one. To the extent any linked websites you visit are not owned or controlled by TJX, we are not responsible for the websites' content, any use of the websites, or the privacy practices of the websites. We suggest you review the privacy policies of any linked websites you visit. 

#### How We Protect Your Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your information. However, we cannot guaranty the effectiveness of these safeguards, and nothing in this statement shall be construed as an express or implied warranty against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

Online access to certain personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone, and we will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited communication.

#### Your Options

To view or update your profile, you can log in to your account to make your changes. You can also ask us to remove your information from our systems by contacting us as described in the Contact Information section.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Statement, or if you wish to update the information you have provided us, you may do so by:

  * Writing to us at the following address:  
The TJX Companies, Inc.  
770 Cochituate Road  
Framingham, MA 01701  
Attn: Customer Service - Privacy Statement 
  * Calling Customer Service Monday – Friday 9:00 AM – 5:00 PM (Eastern Time) at the following toll-free number: 1-800-926-6299.

#### Changes to Our Statement

This privacy statement may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online privacy practices relating to the site. We will post a prominent notice on the site to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Statement and indicate when it was most recently updated.

Effective Date: March 2017
